sabay.com.kh 2019-06-26

# sabay.com – Sabay » Privacy Policy

**Our commitment to privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**The information we collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Sabay online properties. On some pages, you can register, subscribe, make requests, and post comments.

The types of personal information collected are for instance names, email addresses, photos, phone numbers.

**The way we use information:**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in to improve our services.

**Our commitment to data security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Using our content**

To use our article and images you need to contact us in advance and get our approval.

**Your consent**  
By using our online properties, you consent to this online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**How to contact us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, visit our office at 308 Preah monivong Boulevard, Phnom Penh, Cambodia, or send us an email at info@sabay.com.
